question_data = [{"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "A group of islands is called an archipelago.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Republic of Malta is the smallest microstate worldwide.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Vatican City is a country.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The longest place named in the United States is Lake Chargoggagoggmanchauggagoggchaubunagungamaugg, located near Webster, MA.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Mongolia was a part of the now non-existent U.S.S.R.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The capital of the US State Ohio is the city of Chillicothe.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "St. Louis is the capital of the US State Missouri.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Liechtenstein does not have an airport.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The title of the 1969 film Krakatoa, East_of Java is incorrect, as Krakatoa is in fact west of Java.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "question": "Only one country in the world starts with the letter Q.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
